<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ReversiAmovTP</string>
    <string name="reversi">Reversi</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="twoPlayersOff">2 players (offline)</string>
    <string name="twoPlayersOn">2 players (online)</string>
    <string name="threePlayersOn">3 players (online)</string>
    <string name="btnLogin">Sign In</string>
    <string name="etLoginHintPassword">Password</string>
    <string name="etLoginHintEmail">Email</string>
    <string name="tvRegisterLogin">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="tv_forgot_password_login">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="tv_don_t_have_an_account_login">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="tv_already_have_an_account_signup">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="et_username_register">Username</string>
    <string name="et_confirm_password_reg">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="logo">logo</string>
    <string name="rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="game_modes">Game Modes</string>
    <string name="mode_2_players_online">2 Players Online Mode</string>
    <string name="mode_2_players_offline">2 Players Offline Mode</string>
    <string name="mode_3_players_online">3 Players Online Mode</string>
    <string name="special_plays">Special Plays</string>
    <string name="bomb_piece">Bomb piece</string>
    <string name="piece_exchange">Piece exchange</string>
    <string name="rulesText">\tReversi is a board game between two players, in which the objective is to have the greatest number of pieces on the board. Therefore, each player must place a piece in a cell so that, at least in one of the directions (horizontal, vertical, or diagonal), there is a sequence that includes one or more opponent\'s pieces and, on the opposite side, a player\'s piece.</string>
    <string name="mode_2_Offline_text">This game mode is played by two players on a single device on an 8 x 8 board and including the special pieces.</string>
    <string name="mode_2_Online_text">This game mode is played by two players on two different devices on an 8 x 8 board and including the special pieces.</string>
    <string name="mode_3_Online_text">This game mode is played by three players on three different devices, on a 10 x 10 board and including the special pieces.</string>
    <string name="modes_text">At the beginning of the game, the player can choose the game mode he wants to play. Thus, you will have the following game modes as possible choices:</string>
    <string name="special_pieces_text">This game, in addition to the rules already described, also has some special moves, to make the game more competitive.</string>
    <string name="bomb_piece_text">The insertion of a bomb tile can only be performed once by each player during the game and it must be placed on a player\'s tile. When applying this tile, all others within a radius of 1 square are eliminated.</string>
    <string name="piece_exchange_text">Through this special move, the player can exchange two pieces for one of the opponents. This exchange is made once by each player and, when making the exchange, the two pieces that the user wants to exchange are initially marked, followed by the opponent\'s piece.</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="general">General</string>
    <string name="my_account">My Account</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="topscore">TopScore</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
</resources>